(Howard:)Are you crazy?
(Howard:)You don't want
your girlfriend at work with you.
(Howard:)Hell Clam.
(Sheldon:)Why not?
(Sheldon:)Hairy Fairy.
(Raj:)I think it could be romantic.
(Raj:)You know, my parents met
at his place of work.
Your father's a gynecologist.
(Raj:)I know. What started as a pap smear
turned into a date.
(Raj:)Which turned into her working there,
which turned into marriage,
(Raj:)which then turned into hatred,
which continues to this day.
(Raj:)Two-Eyed Cyclops.
(Howard:)Would you please tell him
this isn't a good idea?
(Leonard:)No. I think it'll be great.
(Leonard:)Maybe next time he gets
conjunctivitis at work,
(Leonard:)she can hold his head and try to put
the drops in his eyes.
(Leonard:)Giant baby.
(Sheldon:)That's a Raging Ogre.
(Raj:)I know.
(Howard:)I'm just saying, I'd never want
to work with Bernadette.
(Howard:)Can you imagine seeing
someone all day long
(Howard:)and then you're supposed to hang out
with them after work, too?